gandhi.gov.in 2018-09-23

# Gandhi Time line page

## Terms of use

This website is officially managed by Ministry of Culture, Government of India (hereafter referred to as the ‘Ministry’). This privacy policy describes how the website collects, uses and shares your information when you use it. Website receives your information when you visit it. When using our service you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this privacy policy.   
The website collects no personal information, like names or addresses, when you visit the website. If you choose to provide that information to us, it is used only to fulfil your request for information.  
The Ministry does collect some technical information when you visit the website, to make your experience seamless. The section below explains how we handle and collect technical information when you visit our website.  

Information Collection and usage: 

  * Internet domain
  * IP address
  * Browser type
  * Surfing activity and history
  * Date/time of access
  * Country of access

Website may collect the above information on the basis of usage and may also collect your location-based information for the purpose of: 

  * Customizing the information as per the usage on the website.
  * Statistical data purposes.

**Information the Ministry shares with Third Parties**  
From time to time the Ministry may employ third parties to help them provide or improve the website. These third parties, such as our analytics or hosting provider, may have limited access to databases of user information or registered member information solely for the purpose of helping us provide or improve the website and they will not be able to use the information about our members or visitors for any other purpose. These third parties may collect information sent by your browser or mobile devices such as cookies, your IP address or device ID.  
The Ministry may disclose Personal Information in some other limited circumstances, but the Ministry will specifically describe them to you when it collects the information, such as in the terms of use for a new service or by revising this Privacy Policy.  
In connection with any legal investigation the Ministry may compromise some information only if the Ministry has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other website users, or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities. Ministry assures the disclosure of the information only when the Ministry believes in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on the website.  
**Security**  
The security of your Information is important to us. The Ministry uses reasonable efforts to secure and maintain your information and location information in a secure environment and have implemented reasonable procedures designed to limit unauthorized access, use or disclosure of your information.   
**Changes to this Policy**  
The Ministry may revise this privacy policy from time to time. The most current version of this policy will govern the Ministry’s use of your information and will always be available here. If the Ministry makes any change to this privacy policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, Ministry will update the same on the website. By continuing to access or use the services after those changes becomes effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
